lifeyo.com 2011-06-10

# About Lifeyo | Let people make websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Scape Networks collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Scape Networks’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Scape Networks’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Scape Networks may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Scape Networks also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Scape Networks does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Scape Networks’s websites choose to interact with Scape Networks in ways that require Scape Networks to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Scape Networks gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website at <http://www.lifeyo.com/> to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Scape Networks – by purchasing a Domain name through our partner Register.com, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Scape Networks collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Scape Networks. Scape Networks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Scape Networks may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Scape Networks may monitor the most popular websites on Lifeyo.com. Scape Networks may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Scape Networks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Scape Networks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Scape Networks’s behalf or to provide services available at Scape Networks’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Scape Networks’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Scape Networks will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Scape Networks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Scape Networks believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Scape Networks, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Scape Networks website and have supplied your email address, Scape Networks may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Scape Networks and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Scape Networks takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Scape Networks uses cookies to help Scape Networks identify and track visitors, their usage of Scape Networks website, and their website access preferences. Scape Networks visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Scape Networks’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Scape Networks’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Scape Networks and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Scape Networks may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Scape Networks’s sole discretion. Scape Networks encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
